Speaker 0: Okay, since we already polished the the second and the third 1. Um
Speaker 0:  Okay. Now I'm going to place the first 1 to me and
Speaker 0:  the 61 next to it. Um, I can't reach the other side. Can you please turn the white thing around?
Speaker 0:  um, I'm sorry you can only polish the
Speaker 0:  face, that is um
Speaker 0:  Facing you. Oh, okay.
Speaker 0:  Okay. Okay. Um, I think I I did it like the first 1 the second 1 and the and the sixth 1. Okay, um the hi Diego.
Speaker 0:  Hi Diego.
Speaker 0:  you um
Speaker 0:  Can you turn the price around?
Speaker 0:  Totally work on that opposite.
Speaker 0:  Oh, okay.
Speaker 0:  I'm going to polish this so it's we have um
Speaker 0:  Another 2 surfaces to polish. Can you turn around that for me? Yes I can.
Speaker 0:  You can start.
Speaker 0:  Do you need any help?
Speaker 0:  Diago
Speaker 0:  this charges like uh polish the 1 we see you. I only this 1 only yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, so um, not the side ones, but when it turns to face you
Speaker 0:  Oh, okay. Yeah. Yeah, I got it. Okay. It's okay.
Speaker 0:  Okay, so we need to do 6 times. I asked him to do 6 times.
Speaker 0:  Yeah, but I mean, I guess since you've already polished like the other size just polish like your remaining ones. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Okay. The remaining 1 is the fourth 1 and the fifth 1 can you hi Tia? Can you help me turn turn it again?
Speaker 0:  Okay. Thank you.
Speaker 0:  Okay, I finished the fourth 1 and we have the last 1 to finish which is um surface 5, can you turn it again?
Speaker 0:  Yes, I can.
Speaker 0:  Okay.
Speaker 0:  Thank you. Okay number 5 finished. I think we completed tasks. Thank you.
Speaker 0:  Okay, great. All right. Have a nice job. We're going to fill up the survey. Yeah.
Speaker 0:  Thank you. Go.
Speaker 0:  a response
Speaker 0:  I'm happy to hear that.
Speaker 0:  Oh, yeah.
Speaker 1: